Guide to the Center for Documentary Studies student projects collection, 1980-2011 and undated RL.01266
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Duke, Fall 2001
  - Duke, HIST 195S, The Coastal South, Fall 2001, 1 box
    Student projects for this course consist of interviews with individuals who live or have lived along the southern coast, specifically the coastal Carolinas. Folders typically contain the student's essays, which explore the themes chosen and the unfolding of the projects, and photographs or other media.
    - Bowlus, Anne; Richards, Elise (Box 62)
      A Life on Harkers Island. One spiral scrapbook enclosed.
    - Gurch, Matthew J. (Box 62)
      Gordon and Goliath: A Hunter's Struggle to Save the Green Swamp of North Carolina
    - Helms, Bari (Box 62)
      War and Marriage at Cherry Point
    - Levinson, Josh (Box 62)
      North Carolina Fisherman: Four Portraits
    - Rue, Elena (Box 62)
      Venturing to Deltaville, Virginia Through the Lens of a Camera
    - Way, Annie (Box 62)
      Change and Adaptation, the Life of Pat Scoggins: English War Bride and Coastal Southerner. One microcassette enclosed.
  - Duke, ARTVIS 117: Bullock's BBQ, Lotze, Andrew, Fall 2001, 24 prints
    Contains black-and-white photographs of Bullock's BBQ, a restaurant in Durham, N.C. established in 1952 that specializes in "Southern cooking and catering." Prints are not captioned.
    - Bullock's BBQ photographic prints, 2001, 24 prints (Box 62)
  - (Duke, Fall 2001 - Unidentified class)
    - Bell, Jennifer (Box 46)
      "Patriotism (post Sept. 11)." Chapel Hill, N.C.
    - Fenequito, Lina, 5 folders (Box 63)
      "Faith after the Fall." Black-and-white prints.
    - Hwang, Helen (Box 46)
      "George Watts Elementary School." Durham, N.C.
    - Lee, Mary K. (Box 46)
      "Kinetic Kultur" and "Dale Earhardt Memorial." Durham, Fairmont and Fayetteville, N.C.
    - Mendonca, Adrienne (Box 46)
      "The Last Parade." "Cemetery Photography." "Sept. 11, 2001." Chapel Hill, Hillsborough and Carrboro, N.C.
    - Plaxico, Will (Box 46)
      "Walltown Children's Theater." Durham, N.C.
    - Powers, John (Box 46)
      "N.C. State Fair." Raleigh, N.C.
    - Rue, Elena (Box 66)
      "Multi-racial and Gay Parent Family." Three black-and-white prints.
    - Witheiler, Matthew (Box 46)
      "Behind the Scenes: Aurora." Chapel Hill, N.C. Slide format only.
    - Unidentified author (Box 62)
      Three CD-roms enclosed.
- Duke, Spring 2002
  - Duke, HIST 106S, Wars on the Homefront (1940-2001), Spring 2002, 3 boxes
    Student projects for this course taught by David Cecelski consist of interviews with individuals who lived through wars from 1940-2001, specifically World War II, Vietnam, and the attack on the World Trade Center. Folders typically contain the student's essays, which explore the themes chosen and the unfolding of the projects, and sometimes CD-roms or other media.
    - Bennet, Scott; Post, Kevin (Box 63)
      U-Boats Off Our Coast. One CD-Rom enclosed.
    - Carpenter, Michael (Box 63)
      Stories of World War II and Vietnam Veterans One CD-Rom enclosed.
    - Cockerill, Sarah (Box 63)
      1 spiral notebook enclosed.
    - Corpening, Katherine (Box 64)
      A Human Tragedy Not a National Tragedy [1 spiral scrapbook enclosed.
    - Cutrona, Dante (Box 64)
      In Search of the Cold War: An American Era All Too Easily Forgotten
    - DeMent, James (Box 64)
      The Center of a Vet: Encounters at the Raleigh Vet Center
    - Gilman, Georgia (Box 64)
      Portraits of World War II Veterans
    - Hackett, Kate (Box 64)
      World War II: A Female Perspective
    - Hartman, Conor D. (Box 64)
      Rye Country Day School, Thoughts on 9/11. One VHS tape enclosed.
    - Horn, Brendan (Box 64)
      The Reaction of American Muslims to the September 11th Attacks: A Collection of Six Short Interviews
    - Mabe, Meredith, 2 folders (Box 64)
      A Whole New World Experience: An Interview with Mr. Felix Subervi, World War II Veteran. Three CD-roms enclosed.
    - Ramby, Sarah (Box 65)
      Interview of William Herrara Beardal. Spiral scrapbook contains transcript of interview, plus a timeline of the Vietnam Conflict.
    - Reid, Brittany; Timmerman, Catherine (Box 65)
      A Soldier and a Hero: The Changing Face of the American Veteran. Essay with extracts from oral history interviews with half a dozen veterans of different wars.
    - Smith, Stacy (Box 65)
      From the Mother County to the Empirial [sic] City. Oral history interview with an African American woman, Alma Atkinson Jones, from Elizabethtown, Bladen County. Spiral scrapbook contains maps, color snapshots, photocopies of historical images, captions, and quotations from the interview transcript, also housed in the project folder.
    - Taylor, Kerry (Box 65)
      Raymond Lee Eurquhart--War Resister. Essay and oral history interview with Raymond Lee Eurquhart concerning the Vietnam Conflict. Also includes photocopies of archival documents (letters and clippings).
    - Ward, April Renee (Box 65)
      Little Buoys in Pearl Harbor. Essay and oral history interview with Carroll Robbins Jones on her childhood experience in World War II.
    - Unidentified (Box 65)
      The Shadow of the World Trade Center. Essay and extracts of interviews with witnesses to the September 11, 2001 attack on the World Trade Center in New York City. Includes images of the interviewees and scenes from that day embedded in the text.
  - DiGiovanni, Laura (Box 46)
    "Mrs. Das's Kindergarten Class." Durham, N.C. Slides in addition to prints.
  - Findly, Robert Ross (Box 46)
    "Seagrove." Seagrove, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Fuller, Jessica (Box 46)
    "Memorials." Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Rich, Sarah (Box 46)
    "3 year old classroom- Duke School for Children." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
- UNC, Spring 2002
  - UNC AMST 150 (Box 65)
    - Young, Kristin (Box 65)
      "Final Project." One-page essay on her project, which mixes popular music pieces with commentary about the 9/11 attacks and military service. One CD-rom enclosed.
    - Unidentified author, untitled project (Box 65)
      Spiral notebook with mini-disk included. Journal contains entries reflecting on the process of finding interviewees and developing a focused topic and a set of questions. Topic chosen seems to have to do with World War II and women's roles.
  - UNC FOLK 295 (Box 65)
    - Starnes, Sarah (Box 65)
      "The 'White Girls'." Essay in which "three sisters tell about their WWII home front experience in Locker, Texas."
- Duke, Fall 2002
  - ARTVIS 118S (Box 65)
    - Fattal, Alex, 35 slides (Box 65)
      Images on color slides seems to come from a school and a kitchen. There is no other information with this untitled project.
    - Lopez, Jennifer, 19 prints (Box 65)
      Black-and-white contact prints of construction workers on housing project. Prints measure 8x10 inches.
  - Horton, Cheryl Lynn (Box 46)
    "Love and Strength." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
- Duke, Spring 2003
  - DOCST 177S: Advanced Documentary Photography, Tom Rankin
    Release forms for this class are in box 65. The projects are physically housed in a number of differently-sized boxes for best housing.
    - Cooperrider, Kensy (Box 66)
      Four black-and-white prints depicting storefront churches, at least one of which is in Durham, N.C. Two of the prints are mounted on board.
    - Leshin, Benjamin (Box 65)
      Five uncut square black-and-white contact prints depicting railroad locations in Durham, N.C. such as sidings and tracks.
    - Leshin, Ben, 20 prints (Box 75)
      "Final Project." The square black-and-white contact prints measure between 6 to 7 inches and are mounted on 11x14 inch white boards; they also depict rail transportation locations in Durham, N.C.
    - Raul, Claire (Box 66)
      3 black-and-white prints.
- Duke, Fall 2003
  - Duke, DOCST 198, Documenting the Civil Rights Movement in North Carolina, Fall 2003, 2 boxes
    Student projects for this course consist of interviews with individuals who were directly involved in the Civil Rights Movement in North Carolina. Folders typically contain CD-Roms or other media, and the student's project statements, which explore the themes chosen and the unfolding of the projects.
    - Avalone, Wallis; Sholtes, Joel; Silver, Ben; Wilmer, Melanie (Box 55)
      Interviews with Rev. Roosevelt Alston, Ruth Burt, Henrietta Clark, Dr. James Green, Betty Gregory [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Avalone, Wallis; Silver, Ben (Box 55)
      Interview with Betty Gregory: "Remember That I Loved" [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Avalone, Wallis; Silver, Ben (Box 55)
      Interview with Ruth Burt: "Remember Me as a Humanitarian" [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Wilmer, Melanie (Box 55)
      Interview with Henrietta Clark: "Remember Me as a Good Citizen" [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Sholtes, Joel (Box 55)
      Interview with Rev. Roosevelt Alston [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Butler, Caroline (Box 55)
      Interview with Rev. Carrie Bolton [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Cambridge, Shannon (Box 55)
      Interview with Rev. David C. Forbes, Sr. [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Cook, Colleen (Box 56)
      Interview with Harold Medland [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Daniels, Derek J. (Box 56)
      Interview with Thomas Mason [1 audio microcassette enclosed.
    - Gorod, Adam J. (Box 56)
      Interview with Harold Moore [2 audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Sanders, Crystal (Box 56)
      Interview with Jim Grant [5 audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Saunders, Selaine (Box 56)
      Interview with Fred Battle [1 audio cassette enclosed.
    - Yoffie, Adam Gabriel (Box 56)
      Interview with Dr. Carolyn Guntham Ennis [1 audio cassette enclosed.
  - Documentary Studies 164s (Box 47)
    - Allen, David (Box 47)
      "All of Us Are Motivated by Hope" Rev. Charles Kilburn Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Beutin, Lyndsey (Box 47)
      "A Transformation of the Heart: An Oral History with Rebecca Reyes" Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Bouchard, Richard (Box 47)
      "North Carolina Activism Project: Social Motivation Interview" Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - D'Augusta, Ariana (Box 47)
      "Educational Activism: An Interview with Lisa Lord" Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Fisher, Anne (Box 47)
      Interview with Kristine Stiles. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Fry, Suzanna (Box 47)
      "Born and Raised in Love with the North Carolina Coast: Todd Miller." Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Hueckel, Julia (Box 47)
      "Engage. Conversations with an Activist." [Phillip Shabazz] Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Jantarasami, Lesley (Box 47)
      "In Search of Environmental Justice: The Voice of Nan Freeland." Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - King, Elizabeth (Box 47)
      "Interview with Melinda Wiggins." Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Patel, Kavita (Box 47)
      "Hear my Voice, Follow my Example: Integrated Excerpts from Two Interviews with Steve Bader." Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Paul, Christopher (Box 47)
      "Freedom Ain't Free." [Interview with Ray Eurquhart]Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Paxton, Jamie (Box 47)
      "Conversations with Robin Kirk, Human Rights Activist." Audio cassettes enclosed.
  - Hsu, David (Box 46)
    "Defining Movement: A Duke Dance Group." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
- Duke, Spring 2004
  - Duke, DOCST 117, Documenting Southern Culture, Spring 2004, 1 box
    Student projects for this course consist of photographs capturing various communities within and traits of the American South. Folders contain black-and-white photographs measuring 5x7 and 8x10 inches, and the student's project statements, which explore the themes chosen and the unfolding of the projects.
    - Bloche, David (Box 72)
    - Della Ratte, Renee (Box 72)
      Mexican Community in Durham
    - Klenow, Megan (Box 72)
      Civil War Reenactments
    - Rogers, Jessica (Box 72)
      Waffle House--Midnight
    - Schlendorf, Andrew M. (Box 72)
      Rougemont, N.C.
    - Stallman, Tim (Box 72)
      Durham Construction (Off 15-501)
    - Stallman, Tim (Box 72)
      Kentucky Cockfighting
    - Strange, Lauren (Box 72)
      White Star Portfolio
    - Williams, B. Danielle, 2 folders. (Box 72)
      Southern Mormons
    - Yates Coley, Rebecca (Box 72)
      Tobacco Warehouses
  - Documentary Studies 164s (Box 48)
    - Alexander, Nicholas (Box 48)
      "Daddy's Little Girl: the Struggles of a Civil Rights Leader's Daughter." [Charmaine McKissick] Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Andrews, Margaret (Box 48)
      Interview with Page McCullough. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Gorod, Adam J. (Box 48)
      "The Struggle for Justice: The Life and Work of James Andrews." Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Harris, Kelley (Box 48)
      Interview with Dan Pollitt. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Harrell, Khadidja Latise (Box 48)
      Interview with Elizabeth Freeman Lambar. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Hodgman, Kim (Box 48)
      "A Conversation with Joe Straley." Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Howe, Caitlin (Box 48)
      Interview with Cynthia Brown. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Martinez, Eliana (Box 49)
      Interview with Lonna Harkrader. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Noel, Kimberly (Box 49)
      Interview with Ann Atwater. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Oliver II, Gerald Lee (Box 49)
      "Bound and Determined: An Oral History of the Life and Work of Angela Dunston." Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Scharrer, Jim (Box 49)
      Interview with Al McSurely. Audio cassettes enclosed.
  - Photographing the Lives of Women/Girls, PPS 196
    - Connors, Julia (Box 49)
      "It's a Mutual Thing: Stories of Adoption." Location unknown.
    - Hainsfurther, Jennifer (Box 49)
      "Stolen Moments." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
    - Horton, Cheryl Lynn (Box 49)
      "Spring Forth Farm." Location unknown. Slide format only.
    - Stuart, Julia (Box 49)
      "Signs of Life." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Documentary Studies 190S.02: Black Labor History Fieldwork
    - Biernesser, Ryan (Box 50)
      "Interview of Mary Walker Smith." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Cambridge, Shannon (Box 50)
      "Interview of Nathanette Mayo." Chapel Hill, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Ogunsile, Joy (Box 50)
      "Interview of Ann Atwater." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Proxmire, William (Brocky) (Box 50)
      "Interview of Charles Gooch." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Rauh, Claire (Box 50)
      "Interview of Jackie Caroll-Garcia." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Sobel, Corey (Box 50)
      "Interview of Gloria Robinson, Duke Health." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
- Duke, Spring 2005
  - DOCST 117, Documentary Photography and the Southern Cultural Landscape, Spring 2005, 2 boxes
    Student projects for this course consist of photographs capturing various communities within and traits of the American South. Folders typically contain black-and-white photographs measuring 8x10 inches, and the student's project statements, which explore the themes chosen and the unfolding of the projects.
    - Campbell, Strouse (Box 73)
      Barns
    - Dlugokecki, Anne N. (Box 73)
      Southern Village
    - Dlugokecki, Anne N., 3 folders (Box 75)
      Matted prints measure 9x12 inches.
    - Granbery, Emmie (Box 73)
      World of Cows
    - Godfrey, Meg (Box 73)
      Trash? In the Eye of the Beholder
    - Keffelew, Aeden (Box 73)
      Agape Corner
    - Lane, Diana (Box 73)
      Raleigh State Fairgrounds
    - Reischer, Hollen (Box 73)
      Marked: Subculture of the South
    - Roark, Robin (Box 73)
      A Portrait of Charlie's
    - Rosenberg, Dana (Box 73)
      Visitors: Please Report to the Main Office
    - Samsa, Mary Beth (Box 73)
      John Jefferies and the Occoneechee Native American Tribe
    - Sichel, Corianna (Box 73)
      Lines in Life
    - Silver, Jessica (Box 73)
      Wal-Mart
    - Shah, Amar (Box 73)
      Urban Ministries of Durham Kitchen
    - Tabacaru, Catinca (Box 73)
      The Funeral
    - Templeton, Irka (Box 73)
      DATA
  - Documentary Studies 190S.01: Civil Rights and Labor Struggles, 1 box
    - Chien, Jennifer (Box 51)
      "Interview of Brenda Armstrong, Civil Rights Activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Grant, Mary (Box 51)
      "Hidden Displays of Agency - Darelle Lindsey Oral History." Durham, N.C. Audio cassette enclosed.
    - Griffith, Kimberly (Box 51)
      "Interview of Theresa El-Amin, Union Organizer and Civil Rights Activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Markham, Aaron (Box 51)
      "Interview of Gerald Taylor, Civil Rights Activist and Community Organizer." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed] [Must obtain interviewee's permission to quote or publish piece.]
    - Newman, Bridget (Box 51)
      "Interview of Demoncio Akins, Duke Bus Driver and UNC Student." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Pearson, Tim (Box 51)
      "Interview of Mark Nielson." Durham, N.C. Audio cassette enclosed.
    - Prizer, Timothy (Box 51)
      "Interview of Fernando Bribiezca, UNITE HERE organizer." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed
    - Williams, Charisse (Box 51)
      "Interview of Ajamu Dillahunt, North Carolina Activist and Labor Organizer." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Wright, Lydia (Box 51)
      "Interview of Reggie Cameron, Former Angelica Worker, UNITE HERE organizer." Durham, N.C. Audio cassette enclosed.
- Duke, Spring 2006
  - Documentary Studies 190S.01: Civil Rights and Labor Struggles, 1 box
    - Bueso, Leah (Box 52)
      "Interview of Kohar Parra, Latino community activist, co-chair Durham CAN." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Chao, Andrew (Box 52)
      "Interview of Mandy Carter, Longtime activist with SONG, HRC, peace, civil rights, and LGBT rights." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Cobrand, Cherisse (Box 52)
      "Interview of Natasha Ben, NOLA and NOLA diaspora community activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Davidson, Margaret (Box 52)
      "Interview of Brenda Howerton Community activist, co-chair of Durham CAN." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Falae, Adebola (Box 52)
      "Interview of Olivia Vaughn, Duke Housekeeping activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Lumpkin, Emily (Box 52)
      "Interview of Pam Broom, NOLA (New Orleans, LA) and NOLA diaspora community activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Riess, Jessica (Box 52)
      "Interview of Dr. William Turner, Duke Divinity school professor and longtime civil rights activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Selker, Lee (Box 52)
      "Interview of Ray Eurquhardt, longtime labor and community activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Williams, Neil (Box 52)
      "Interview of Farad Ali, Black entrepreneur and community activist." Durham, N.C. Audio cassettes enclosed.
- Duke, Spring 2007
  - Capstone Project, Certificate of Documentary Studies: Durham Skateboard Scene, Strouse Campbell, Spring 2007, 11 prints
    Consists of prints of skateboarders and graffiti artists around the city of Durham, N.C. and on Duke's campus. Digital inkjet color prints measure 17x22 inches and are housed in 20x24 inch window mats.
    - Durham Skateboard Scene, 2007, 11 prints (Box 77)
  - Documentary Studies 190S.06: Civil Rights & Labor Struggles, 1 box
    - Cater, Reid (Box 53)
      Transcending Stereotypes: The Activist Path of Melinda Wiggins
      Audio cassettes enclosed.
    - Cronin, Kevin (Box 53)
      Unlikely Individual, Unlikely Results: The Oral History of Bob Hall and Activism in the South
    - Goldberg, Cameron (Box 53)
      Crossing Racial Boundaries: The Connections We Must Find to Create Equality and American Success
    - Griffin, Eric (Box 53)
      Making Sense of Struggle: Radical Black Activism in the Labor Movement
    - Mkrtchian, Edgar (Box 53)
      We Cannot Walk Alone: Uneasy Alliances and Their Role in Civil Rights and Labor Struggles in Durham
    - Salvi, Tiarrah D. (Box 53)
      Barbara-Nayo: A Change Agent Seeking the Truth Through Art and Activism
- Duke, Fall 2007
  - The South in Black and White: Bluegrass: The Culture of Music, Nettles, Kim
    Contains color photographs taken at bluegrass festivals and concerts. Print titles and captions are located on accompanying title list. Digital inkjet prints measure 13x19 inches.
    - Bluegrass: The Culture of Music color photographic prints, 2010, 28 prints (Box 59)
- UNC, Fall 2007
  - UNC FOLK 690, The Coastal South, 1 box
    Student projects for this University of North Carolina, CDS-sponsored course consist of oral history interviews with individuals who live or have lived along the Southern coast, specifically the coastal Carolinas. Project folders typically contain interviews on CD-ROMs or other media, along with student essays which explore the process of choosing a theme and the unfolding of the documentary work.
    - Brown, Whitney (Box 57)
      Interviews with Rudy Austin and Lindsey Howard
      Two audio cassettes and one CD-Rom enclosed.
    - Hellmich, Paul (Box 57)
      Interview with Rebecca Drane Warren
      One CD-Rom enclosed.
    - Hellmich, Paul (Box 57)
      Interview with Francis Drane Inglis
    - Honea, Sean (Box 57)
      Interviews with C. Rudolph Knight; Lawrence Auld, Ph.D.; Bernard and Annie Mae Harrison
      Two CD-Roms enclosed.
    - Honea, Sean (Box 57)
      Interviews with Helen P. Gay, Mae Parker, and Myrtle C. Lancaster
      Four CD-Roms enclosed.
    - Melzer, Ashley (Box 57)
      Interviews with Ruthie and John DeMaria
    - Safron, Helena (Box 57)
      Interview with Vivian Johnson
    - Safron, Helena (Box 57)
      Interview with LaVerne Stokley
    - Safron, Helena (Box 57)
      Interview with Larry Tucker
- Duke, Spring 2008
  - Independent Study: Portrait of TROSA, Silver, Jessica, 1 box
    Contains photographic color portraits of male and female residents of Triangle Residential Options for Substance Abusers (TROSA). The prints are signed and captioned by the portrait sitter. Captions are meant to answer the question "What does this photograph say about you?" Digital inkjet color prints measure 13x19 inches.
    - Portrait of TROSA color photographic prints, 2008, 20 prints (Box 60)
- Duke, Spring 2009
  - Behind the Veil: Methods
    Scope and Contents
    "Behind the Veil: Methods," instructor Max Krochmal.
    - Moncure event video, tapes 1 and 2, 2009-04-29; Two mini-dv video tapes. (Box 78)
    - Recordings and documents (Digital-materials RL01266-SET-0001, E-folder RL01266-DVD-0002, E-folder Moncure BTV)
- Duke, Fall 2009
  - Southern Culture Through Photography: Timberwood Organics, Rappaport, Alex, 1 box
    Project consists of color photographs taken at Timberwood Organics, an organic farm in Efland, North Carolina that is owned by Ray Christopher. Digital inkjet prints measure 13x19 inches and are not captioned. Also contains a CD-Rom with the image files.
    - Timberwood Organics color photographic prints, 2009, 24 prints (Box 61)
  - Duke DOCST 135S, Intro to Audio Documentary, 2 folders
    Contains two CD-Roms housing student final audio project files. The class was taught by Professor John Biewen.
    - Final audio projects, 2 CD-Roms (Box 74)
- Duke, Spring 2010
  - Capstone Project, Certificate of Documentary Studies: Illumination, Jennifer Kozin, .5 box